T.J. Robinson

NETWORK ADMINISTRATOR | I.T. SUPPORT

(818) 471-2113

Van Nuys, California

in linkedin.com/in/tj-robins0n

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Certified Bitcoin Professional (8a9703) and Cybersecurity Analyst with over 5 years experience mining, trading, and researching cryptocurrencies. In my most recent position, I utilized OSINT to conducted investigations to identify multimillion-dollar piracy networks. I am familiar with multiple industry compliance standards including HIPPA and PCI-DSS.

EDUCATION

Cybersecurity, Certificate

UCLA Extensions Los Angeles, California 2020-Present

Business Management, B.S.

Penn Foster College Scottsdale, Arizona 2020-Present

CORE SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL

Creative Problem Solving Critical Thinking Leadership Orientated Self-Motivated Help Desk / Support

COMPUTER

Microsoft Office Excel Spreadsheets Linux | Windows Salesforce

EXTRA

CERTIFICATIONS

Comptia CySA+ CCNA AWS Solutions Architect -Associate

WORK EXPERIENCE

NETWORK OPERATIONS TECHNICIAN

Multacom Corporation / Los Angeles, CA / 2018-Present

- Responsible for providing essential network monitoring, problem identification and resolution, as well as acting as the company technical interface for Multacom Corporation customer base.
- Carry out administration tasks such as software installation/updates, security patches, and hardware maintenance on Windows and Linux operating systems.
- Assist in the deployment, integration, and initial configuration of new security solutions and enhancements to existing security solutions in accordance with standard best operating procedures and corporate security documents.

INTERNET INVESTIGATOR

Motion Picture Association / Sherman Oaks, CA / 2021

- Assist Global Content Protection in protecting the motion picture and television industry's business activities by investigating and reporting on individuals and organizations engaged in copyright infringement.
- Retain strict cover and confidentiality regarding all cases and any other sensitive information before, during, and after each case.
- Identified cases suitable for further investigation or escalated actions, including civil and criminal actions.
- Document cases using Salesforce software.

MAINTENANCE UTILITY WORKER

Athens Services / Sun Valley, CA / 2017-2018

- Under direction of Maintenance Department Management performed complex preventative maintenance tasks. Personally, troubleshot and repaired a wide variety of operational equipment.
- Provided support to the plant maintenance department by installing and repairing electrical systems, apparatuses, and electrical and electronic components of machinery and equipment while following electrical code, manuals, schematic diagrams, and blueprints.
- Operated a variety of hand tools, power tools, and electrical and electronic testing equipment.

TRANSCRIPT OF RECORD

Page 1of 1

DATE: 5 Apr 2020

STUDENT NAME: TAIDJE ROBINSON

STUDENT ID: X1898936

SCHOOL ID:

COURSE NUMBER	TITLE	START DATE	END DATE	GRADE	HOURS	UNITS	CEU
COM SCI X 420.1	FUNDAMENTALS OF CYBERSECURITY	25 Jun 2019	03 Sep 2019	A-	36.0	4.00	3.60
COM SCI X 420.5	NETWORK, O/S AND DB SECURITY	23 Sep 2019	23 Dec 2019	Α	36.0	4.00	3.60
COM SCI X 420.3	INFO SYS INFRASTRUCTURE SECURITY MGMNT	24 Sep 2019	03 Dec 2019	A+	36.0	4.00	3.60
COM SCI X 460.1	ARCHITECTING CLOUD SOLUTIONS USING AWS	06 Jan 2020	09 Mar 2020	A+	36.0	4.00	3.60

UCLA EXTENSION UNOFFICIAL TRANSCRIPT